The enemy is everywhere.
Ambush is a war, action, thriller film directed by Mark Burman.
When a small outpost is ambushed, a US Army squad must take the battle below ground on a
high-stakes mission in a new type of warfare the likes of which they have never seen.
Miller, played by Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
Ackerman, played by Connor Paolo.
Capitaine Drummond, played by Aaron Eckhart.
Bian Fam, played by Mara Lane.
Gates, played by Patrick Walker.
Boyd, played by Jason Genao.
Ambush is a 2023 American action war film produced and directed by Mark Earl Burman and
written by Burman, Michael McClung, Johnny Lozano, and Dillon Slack.
It stars Jonathan Rhys Meyers, Connor Paolo, and Aaron Eckhart.
The tone is intense.